She's a risk they had to take.
Spy is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Paul Feig.
A desk-bound CIA analyst volunteers to go undercover to infiltrate the world of
a deadly arms dealer, and prevent diabolical global disaster.
Susan Cooper, played by Melissa McCarthy.
Raina Boyanov, played by Rose Byrne.
Rick Ford, played by Jason Statham.
Bradley Fine, played by Jude Law.
Nancy B. Artingstall, played by Miranda Hart.
Elaine Crocker, played by Allison Janney.
Spy is a 2015 American spy  action comedy film
written and directed by Paul Feig.
It stars Melissa McCarthy, Jason Statham, Rose Byrne, and Jude Law, alongside Miranda Hart, Bobby Cannavale,
Peter Serafinowicz, Morena Baccarin, Nargis Fakhri, and Allison Janney in supporting roles.
The film follows unorthodox secret agent Susan Cooper (McCarthy) as
she tries to trace a stolen portable nuclear device.
Produced by Peter Chernin, Jenno Topping, Feig, and Jessie Henderson, Spy had its world premiere at South by Southwest on
March 15, 2015, and was theatrically released in the United States on June 5, 2015, by 20th Century Fox.
Spy received praise for Feig's direction and screenplay, McCarthy and Byrne's
performances, as well as Statham's unexpectedly comedic performance.
The film grossed $235 million worldwide against a $65 million budget.
It was nominated for two Golden Globe Awards: Best Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy
and Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy for McCarthy.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia), budapest,
hungary, paris, france, undercover agent, rome, italy.
The tone is lighthearted.